const englishPhrasalVerbsQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is the meaning of the phrasal verb 'break down'?",
    options: [
      "To divide into smaller parts",
      "To stop working",
      "To analyze thoroughly",
      "To speed up",
    ],
    correct_option: "To stop working",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following sentences uses the phrasal verb 'give up' correctly?",
    options: [
      "He gave down on his dreams.",
      "She gave up to her favorite hobby.",
      "They gave in the game.",
      "I had to give up chocolate for a month.",
    ],
    correct_option: "I had to give up chocolate for a month.",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the phrasal verb 'run out of' mean?",
    options: [
      "To have an excessive supply of something",
      "To find a new source of something",
      "To exhaust the supply of something",
      "To keep a secret",
    ],
    correct_option: "To exhaust the supply of something",
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the correct meaning of 'turn down' as a phrasal verb.",
    options: [
      "To increase the volume",
      "To refuse an offer or request",
      "To flip a switch",
      "To fix something that's broken",
    ],
    correct_option: "To refuse an offer or request",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the meaning of the phrasal verb 'get over'?",
    options: [
      "To become sick",
      "To recover from an illness or emotional distress",
      "To get something from a higher shelf",
      "To avoid a problem",
    ],
    correct_option: "To recover from an illness or emotional distress",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following sentences uses the phrasal verb 'break up' correctly?",
    options: [
      "I need to break up the party at 10 PM.",
      "They had a nice break up in the park.",
      "The teacher asked us to break down the lesson.",
      "Their relationship ended, and they decided to break up.",
    ],
    correct_option: "Their relationship ended, and they decided to break up.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the meaning of the phrasal verb 'go on'?",
    options: ["To stop", "To continue", "To turn around", "To reduce speed"],
    correct_option: "To continue",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the phrasal verb 'look forward to' indicate?",
    options: [
      "To avoid an event",
      "To be uninterested in something",
      "To anticipate something with pleasure",
      "To experience regret",
    ],
    correct_option: "To anticipate something with pleasure",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following sentences uses the phrasal verb 'call off' correctly?",
    options: [
      "We should call off the picnic due to the beautiful weather.",
      "They decided to call off the wedding at the last minute.",
      "The game was called off because of heavy rain.",
      "She called off her friend for a chat.",
    ],
    correct_option: "The game was called off because of heavy rain.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the meaning of the phrasal verb 'run into'?",
    options: [
      "To jog into a room",
      "To have an unexpected encounter or meeting with someone",
      "To run quickly away from a situation",
      "To investigate a case",
    ],
    correct_option: "To have an unexpected encounter or meeting with someone",
  },
];
export default englishPhrasalVerbsQuestions;
